ITALIAN CUISINE
TRENDY
100 METERS TO THE LEFT
ITALIAN CUISINE
TRENDY
TODAY'S MENU
DINER DEPENDENT
WITH COFFEE & DESSERT
3,500 YEN—
EPISODE 10
LET'S GO EAT SOME ITALIAN FOOD
INGREDIENTS
• MOZZARELLA CHEESE
(4 PIECES, THINLY SLICED)
• TOMATO (5 PIECES, THINLY SLICED)
TONIO'S SPECIAL HOUSE DRESSING
• 1 ANCHOVY FILLET • WAKAME
• OLIVE OIL • WHITE WINE VINEGAR
• LEMON JUICE • SALT • PEPPER
• BASIL (ON TOP) • TOASTED BREAD
• LETTUCE (FOR GARNISH)
(SERVE IMMEDIATELY)
MORIOH LANDMARK 3
"ITALIAN RESTAURANT TRENDY"
HOW TO GET THERE: 1 MINUTE'S WALK
FROM MAIN STOP OFF POINT OF MORIOH
KUNIMI MOUNTAIN PASS CEMETARY BUS
AN ECCENTRIC RESTAURANT WHERE
THERE IS NO SET MENU,
AND WHERE THE CHEF DECIDES
HIS MENU ON THE BASIS OF
EACH CUSTOMER'S PHYSICAL CONDITION.
SEATING IS LIMITED.
RESERVATIONS ARE RECOMMENDED.
INGREDIENTS
• SPAGHETTI • PITTED BLACK OLIVES
• OLIVE OIL • ANCHOVY FILLET
• GARLIC • CHILI FLAKES
• CHERRY TOMATOES
• PARSLEY, SALT, PEPPER
• PARMESAN CHEESE
(SERVE PIPING HOT)
ROME
NAPLES
SPAGHETTI TAGLIATELLE LINGUINE
FUSILLI PENNE FARFALLE
LASAGNE CONCHIGLIE TUBETTI
MEDICATED
TRENDY
POLE JAM
EPISODE 11
CHILI PEPPER, PART 1